Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: How we have served, Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The AFL in the 1920s, Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Trade unions, Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Trade unions, Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 2)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous speeches, articles, flyers, news clippings, Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 3)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Hollywood at the crossroads, Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 4)
    Author: Irving Bernstein
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: flyers and speeches, Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 5)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Industrial education, Publication (Box 5.1, Folder 6)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous media releases about American Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 6, Folder 1)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of Conference of International Representatives, A.F. of L. to consider tentative draft American Federation of Labor internal disputes plan, Chicago, Illinois, May 14, 1954, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Notes: Copy 2
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: news clippings, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: American labor looks at the world, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: For peace and freedom, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: The A.F. of L. at work towards democracy in Germany, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: The rights of labor, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Author: American Federation of Labor. International Labor Relations Committee
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous reports, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: news clippings; flyer, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the National Committee of Labor's League for Political Education: St. Paul Auditorium, October 5, 1949, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Author: Labor's League for Political Action
  - Item 2: Plan for improved health insurance for all, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: press releases, flyers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Here's the answer, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: press releases, flyers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the National Committee of Labor's League for Political Education: San Francisco Auditorium September 24, 1951, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Author: Labor's League for Political Education
    Notes: 2 copies
  - Item 2: National Committee meeting, Labor's League for Political Education: Hamilton Hotel, Washington, D.C., November 1, 1951, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: press releases, flyers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: press releases, flyers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Political memo, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: press releases, flyers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: press releases, flyers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: L.L.P.E. Political Tipsheets, Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.1-14
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: news clippings, Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Publications relating to American Federation of Labor, Office of the General Counsel, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Taft-Hartley law exposed!, Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Author: J. Albert Woll
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Legal information bulletin, Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: America needs a just labor law, Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Our program for social security, Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: press releases, flyers, Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Revision of the fair labor standards act, Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Item 5: The A F of L case for a just labor law, Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: The position of the American Federation of Labor on the Little Steel Formula, Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A[merican] F[ederation] of L[abor] looks ahead, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Convict labor, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Has the non-unionist a right to work how, when, and where he pleases?, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Author: Frank K. Foster
  - Item 4: Labor and the courts, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Labor and the national emergency, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Recommended report for the Presidential Committee on the Cost of Living, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Some reasons for Chinese exclusion, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: The safety of the future lies in organized labor, Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Author: Henry Demarest Lloyd
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade unions: their origin and objects, influence and efficacy; 6th ed., Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The safety of the future lies in organized labor, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Trade unions: their origin and objects, influence and efficacy; 2nd ed., Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Address delivered at the American Federation of Labor Convention, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Henry W.Blair
  - Item 5: History and philosophy of the eight-hour movement, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Lemuel Danryid
  - Item 6: Official book of the American Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Philosophy of trade unions, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Dyer D. Lum
  - Item 8: The condition of women workers under the present industrial system, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Ida M. Van Etten
  - Item 9: The eight hour primer, Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: George E. McNeill
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: An open letter to ministers of the gospel., Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Disarmament, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Industry's manifest duty, from the Report of the Executive Council to the Convention of the American Federation of Labor, beginning in Portland, Ore., October 1, 1923, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: 55 questions and answers on campaign issues, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Education for all, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Labor and education, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Author: American Federation of Labor. Committee on Education
  - Item 7: Labor and the national emergency, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Study and report for American Federation of Labor upon judicial control over legislatures as to Constitutional questions, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Author: Jackson H. Ralston
  - Item 9: The American labor movement, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: The initiative, referendum and recall, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: The social problem, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Author: National Civic Federation. Industrial Economics Dept.
  - Item 12: The Union label: its history and aims; prize essays, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Tuberculosis, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Union insurance, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Union management cooperation, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Wage negotiations and practices, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A. F. of L. at the crossroads., Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Author: Rand School of Social Science. Current History Class Committee
  - Item 2: Address of Hon. Robert. M. La Follette, of Wisconsin, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Author: Robert M. La Follette
  - Item 3: Involuntary servitude in Colorado, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Legislative achievements of American Federation of Labor. [1925], Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Legislative achievements of the American Federation of Labor [1920], Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Letters to a bishop, Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade union epigrams, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Author: Walter Macarthur
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous pams to small/brief to catalog, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Principles established by the National Labor Relations Board, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Railroad labor conference, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Unions provide against unemployment, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: When you have a case before a regional labor board, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Workers' interest in safety problems, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Yellow dog contract, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Elections, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Labor on Fascism and Nazism, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Labor's charter of rights, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Analysis of National Industrial Recovery Act, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Confirmation of Hon. John J. Parker to be an associate justice of the Supreme court of the United States, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Author: United States. Congress. Senate. Committee on the Judiciary
  - Item 3: High wages, the basis of recovery, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Labor planks in the political platforms of the republican and democratic parties and the records of the candidates for president and vice-president, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Non-partisan declarations, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Organized labor's modern wage policy, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Report of the Committee on Shorter Workday, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Southern workers' handbook, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Suggestions on the making of agreements, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: The A. F. of L. in 1931, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Author: Abraham John Muste
  - Item 11: The partner, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Author: Henry Worth Thornton
  - Item 12: To nullify yellow dog contracts, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Author: John P. Frey
  - Item 13: Wage negotiations; do you have the facts?, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 14: Wages and labor's share, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Author: Jrgen Kuczynski
  - Item 15: Yellow dog contracts condemned by experts, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Guide for vocational education, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Labor and culture, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Author: Spencer Miller Jr.
  - Item 3: Labor and education, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Recommendations for state unemployment compensation laws, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Unemployment compensation pooled fund, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Why we must repeal merit rating provisions in unemployment compensation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Workers' education and democracy, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Workmen's compensation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A rainbow pot of gold, or, Dependable income for old age, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: American Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: An idea worth hundreds of dollars, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Consumers' cooperation, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Explanatory comment on American Federation of Labor amendments to the National labor relations act, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: National labor relations act, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Next steps in social insurance, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Organizations affiliated, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: The wage and hour law, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: a couple pamphlets too brief to catalog, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Labor's monthly survey, Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Labour and the war, an address to the American federation of labour, 1942 convention, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Wage negotiations in wartime, Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Author: American Federation of Labor. Research and Information Service
- Congress of American-Soviet friendship, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor's stake in American-Soviet friendship, Publication (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Author: Congress of American-Soviet friendship
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Italian labor today, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Author: Luigi Antonini
  - Item 2: petition and flyers too brief to catalog, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 1945, an epochal year, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: American Federation of Labor views and suggestions to the San Francisco conference for amending the Dumbarton Oaks proposals, May 2, 1945, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Opportunity for education for all, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The position of the American Federation of Labor on the Little Steel Formula, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Health..benefit plans by collective bargaining, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Jobs for the handicapped through collective bargaining, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Les syndicats europeens et americains unis pour le plan Marshall, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Author: Irving Brown
  - Item 4: miscellaneous pams to small/brief to catalog, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Souvenir program of the Sixty-fifth convention of the American Federation of Labor, October 7, 1946, Publication (Box 11, Folder 6)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The American Federationist, 1947; Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Author: The American Federationist
    Notes: v.54:no.6 (1947:June)
  - Item 2: Conference of representatives of national and international unions, the American Federation of Labor on provisions of the Taft-Hartley Act: July 9, 1947, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Report of the conference of national and international unions on educational and political matters. Dec. 5, 1947, Hotel Washington, Washington, D.C., Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Summary of provisions of the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Veterans welcome home, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Voluntary arbitration of labor disputes, Publication (Box 11, Folder 7)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous pams to small/brief to catalog, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: US Labor backs the ERP, Publication (Box 11, Folder 8)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Taft-Hartley law exposed!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: What's wrong with the Taft-Hartley law?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 9)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Education program adopted at the, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: miscellaneous pams to small/brief to catalog, Publication (Box 11, Folder 10)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Book of information and instructions for officers and members of directly affiliated local trade and federal labor unions of the American Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Our program for social security, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: The great tax fraud., Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Author: Arthur A. Edler
  - Item 4: The last five years, Publication (Box 11, Folder 11)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The American federation of Labor and international affairs, Publication (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Author: Jack C. Plano
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous pams to small/brief to catalog, Publication (Box 11, Folder 13)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Pension plans under collective bargaining, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: The "Right to work" wreck!, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: We saw Israel, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Author: William Griffin
  - Item 4: Who gets the tax cuts?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 14)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Conference of International Officers, American Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: miscellaneous pams to small/brief to catalog, Publication (Box 11, Folder 15)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: A "turnover" talk for fair practices, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: How to win, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Author: AFL-CIO. Committee on Political Education
  - Item 3: miscellaneous union flyers and pamphlets to brief to catalog, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Trade unions: their origin and objects, influence and efficacy, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 5: Wage negotiations, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 6: What can I do about it?, Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Notes for speakers, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Publications relating to American Federation of Labor, Office of the General Counsel, Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.1- 5
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: miscellaneous pams to small/brief to catalog, Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: How to organize local unions of the national and international organizations directly affiliated with the American Federation of Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: miscellaneous union flyers and pamphlets to brief to catalog, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Southern workers' handbook, Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor planks in the political platforms of the republican and democratic parties and the records of the candidates for president and vice-president, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: miscellaneous union flyers and pamphlets to brief to catalog, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The International Labor Organization, Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: American federation of labor post-war forum, Hotel Commodore, New York City, April 12th and 13th, 1944, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Democracy and the free labor movement, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Employment after the war, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Author: John Herman Groesbeck Pierson
  - Item 4: Machinery for reconversion, Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Post-war program American Federation of Labor, 1944; Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Notes: 1944 April 12. Copy 2
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A Radio forum conducted by the American Federation of Labor on, Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: President Gompers report to the officers and delegates to the Thirtieth Annual Convention of the American Federation of Labor, 1910; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: President Gompers report to the officers and delegates to the Thirty-First Annual Convention of the American Federation of Labor, 1911; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: President Gompers report to the officers and delegates to the Thirty-Second Annual Convention of the American Federation of Labor, 1912; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: President Gompers report to the officers and delegates to the Twenty-Eighth Annual Convention of the American Federation of Labor, 1908; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: President Gompers report to the officers and delegates to the Twenty-Fourth Annual Convention of the American Federation of Labor, 1904; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: President Gompers report to the officers and delegates to the Twenty-Ninth Annual Convention of the American Federation of Labor, 1909; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: President Gompers report to the officers and delegates to the Twenty-Seventh Annual Convention of the American Federation of Labor, 1907; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Secretary Morrison's report, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: several brief reports not suitable for cataloging, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Subsidized industrial migration, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Author: American Federation of Labor. Subcommittee on Migration and Subsidization of Industry
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Wage negotiations in wartime, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
- AFL (American Federation of Labor), Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A study of actual earnings in Philadelphia Typographical Union, Number 2, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Organized labor's modern wage policy, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)